(
"ai_sub_version": "2.5.0",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 2,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 12,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"web_search_tool": "duckduckgo",
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": "libx264"
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
また悪い夢を見た。
I had another bad dream.
陰惨な現場が日常の探偵という職業には、
For a detective who deals with gruesome scenes daily,
悪夢は付き物と言ってもいいでしょう。
nightmares are just part of the job.
だが、気にしている場合ではない。
But there's no time to dwell on it.
彼女のもとに、また新たな事件が舞い込んできているからだ。
Because new cases are already finding their way to her.
(Unhappy?)
悩める人の子よ
O troubled child of man,
(Unlucky?)
人ならざる者も
and those who are not human as well.
(Be happy!)
絶えず目指せよ
Always aim higher,
生きてるんだろ
you're alive, aren't you?
目を逸らした過去も
The past you turned away from,
退屈な未来も
and the boring future,
抱え込んだまま
carry them both with you.
誰の目も届かない
In the transparent boundary,
透明な境界
where no one's eyes can reach.
一度行ければ
If you can go there once,
独欲の奥
into the depths of your desires.
(Undead!)
ねぇねぇねぇ 何だかんだして
Hey, hey, hey, one way or another,
戦ったりよもやそんな気がするの
I feel like I'm fighting or something.
古の 触れたこともない
The ancient, untouched
感情自分、自分、自分、自分
emotions: myself, myself, myself, myself.
と思う 疾っくに死んでる
I think... already long dead,
透明な幽霊と対面
confronting a transparent ghost.
一対 行ければ 一対 既欲の奥
If I can go, pair by pair, into the depths of desire.
(Undead!)
もういないのに、あれ？
Even though they're gone, huh?
と違いないアイロニー
It's undoubtedly ironic.
目透かされているのは今の自分
It's my current self being seen through.
なんせ急がないで
Anyway, don't rush.
(Undead!)
言わずもがなコンプレックス
Needless to say, a complex.
取り繕われているみたい
Seems to be all patched up,
巻き付いてそのまだ
wrapped around and staying that way.
(Undead!)
死んじゃいない 共鳴と迷の連鎖
Not dead, a chain of resonance and illusions.
生きていることとは
To be alive
変わり続けることだ
is to keep on changing.
不意にアンデッドして満足するなよ
Don't be satisfied with suddenly being undead.
幸せになろうとしなよ ほら
Try to be happy, look.
この世、かの世は奇々怪々ファンタジー
This world and the next are a bizarre fantasy.
次は鬼が出るか蛇が出るか
Will it be a demon or a snake next?
手を取ってさあ始まる物語
Take my hand, the story is about to begin.
正真正銘化物の子よ 後悔ないピースピース
A true child of monsters, no regrets, peace peace!
Past and future
Can't change the past
Run for the future
何だかんだして 未来に何だそんな気がして
One way or another, I feel something about the future.
希望持てないよね ほら気がして
Can't have hope, can I? I just feel it.
もう随分生きてる 消し飛んだテンプレの肖像
I've lived quite a while, a portrait of a blown-away template.
素敵な出来心の手配もない
No arrangements for a wonderful whim.
残念 積んだ経験の因果関係
Too bad, the causality of accumulated experience.
開示された心は退屈な進化
The revealed heart is a boring evolution.
世は刺激が欲しいんだ 飽きちゃった？ 誰だった？
The world wants stimulation. Got bored? Who was it?
なんせ整ってくガイダンス
What well-arranged guidance,
フルコンプライアンス
full compliance.
上書きされていくみたい
Seems like it's being overwritten.
吸い付く視線 あれも これも どれも
Clinging gazes—that, this, all of it.
(Undead!)
…同じ血が流る
...the same blood flows.
Undead
信じらんない お前とお前の連鎖
Unbelievable, the chain of you and you.
いつ世も過去も未来も今にあるんだ
Every age, past and future, is in the now.
生きていることを愚直に果たせよ
Fulfill the act of living honestly.
目指せハッピーエンド Undead
Aim for the happy end, Undead!
信じらんない お前生きているんだ
Unbelievable, you're alive.
幸せを諦めてしまうなら独りあれ
If you're going to give up on happiness, be alone.
さらば苦しみに慣れて耐えているだけじゃ
Farewell, if you're just getting used to suffering...
死んでも同然 死屍累々 Undead
...you're as good as dead. A pile of corpses, Undead!
アンハッピー？ 悩み多き君の今宵
Unhappy? Dealing with a lotta woes tonight.
アンラッキー？ 人ならざる者の開幕
Unlucky? The curtain rises for non-humans.
目指せ平和 生きているんなら
Aim for peace, if you're alive.
誇れ下手な幸せになるのも
Be proud, even of becoming clumsily happy.
どうせ見せ場 お前らここに集え
It's a highlight anyway. Everyone, gather here!
一切合切 合体死ね 見境ピースピースピース
Everything altogether, unite and die, indiscriminate peace!
Past and future, can't change the past
Past and future, run for the future
ひととなり所詮 余命宣告
A person's true self is but a death sentence.
生き抜けこの化け物ばかりの物語
Survive this story full of monsters.
じゃめ じゃめ じゃめ 脳味噌の中から
Jame, jame, jame, from inside the brain...
やめろバカと喚く 蒸らされて
...screaming 'Stop it, idiot!', being steamed.
誰 目 誰 半端なく ラブときらめき
Whose eyes? Whose? No half-measures, love and sparkle.
浮き足立つ フィロソフィー
A restless philosophy.
死ぬほど可愛い 上目遣い 何が正味
Deadly cute upturned eyes, what's the real deal?
触れるくらい ぶちまけらしい 気づけば逃避
Enough to touch, scattered about, escaping before I know.
この世に生まれた君が悪い
It's your fault for being born into this world.
やたらとしんどい 恋煩い バラバラ塗る 頭とこの正体
Excessively painful lovesickness, painting in pieces...
ゲロも吐けない アイラブユー 掻き消して
...can't even vomit. I love you, erase it all.
アイリスアウト
Iris out.
どっしょん この思いを どっしょん 暴れろ
Bang! This feeling. Bang! Go wild.
蛟龍の如定めが 溶けてゲロになりそう
Destiny like a dragon, melting into vomit.
どこ走ったって 溺れ死にそう
No matter where I run, I feel like I'm drowning.
今この世で 君だけ大正解
In this world right now, only you are the big success.
100回書いても 足りやしない
Even if I write it 100 times, it's not enough.
君だけルールは 適応外
The rules don't apply only to you.
奴らもお手上げ 黒白つけ放題
Even they give up, as much black and white as you want.
君が笑顔で あらばそれだけで
If you're smiling, that's enough.
ぶち撒けラブで どこにスティグマも 申し訳ねえな
Scattered love and stigma everywhere, my apologies.
目を覚まして 貫いて ここが満点
Wake up, pierce through, this is a perfect score.
死ぬほど可愛い 上目遣い 何が正味
Deadly cute upturned eyes, what's the real deal?
触れるくらい ぶちまけらしい 気づけば逃避
Enough to touch, scattered about, escaping before I know.
この世に生まれた君が悪い
It's your fault for being born into this world.
なんでもいい なんでもいい 今君と謎解いてる 全てを教えて
Anything's fine, solving mysteries with you, tell me all.
ゲロも吐けない アイラブユー 掻き消して
Can't even vomit. I love you, erase it all.
アイリスアウト
Iris out.
どっしょん この思いを どっしょん 暴れろ
Bang! This feeling. Bang! Go wild.
蛟龍の如定めが 溶けてゲロになりそう
Destiny like a dragon, melting into vomit.
どこ走ったって 溺れ死にそう
No matter where I run, I feel like I'm drowning.
今この世で 君だけ大正解
In this world right now, only you are the big success.
ある殺人事件を調べてほしいという匿名の依頼。
Like this one. An anonymous plea for help in the investigation of a murder.
手紙に被害者の情報はほとんどなく、ましてや犯人の情報は皆無であった。
The letter had little on the victim and nothing on the killer.
あまりに不可解な謎の手紙。
A letter too mysterious and cryptic,
イタズラの可能性もある、けど…
it could even be a prank. But...
おや？
Huh?
おはよう、アーニャ！依頼された絵が完成しましたよ〜。
Good morning, Anya! I finished your commission~~
ニノマエ・イナニス。この町一番の肖像画家だ。
Ninomae Ina'nis. The greatest portrait artist on this side of the tracks.
あの…私の顔に何か付いてます？
Um... is there something on my face?
事件の手がかりがない以上、解決の糸口を見つけるには彼女の才能を頼る必要があった。
With no leads, the detective needed a talent like that to jumpstart her investigation.
アーニャ？
Anya?
とはいえこういった事件では、誰もが容疑者になりうる。
Then again, in a case like this, anyone could be the killer.
そう、この純粋で可憐なイナでさえ…
What if sweet, innocent Ina—
わああーっ！
WAH!
うわっ！
Ah!
ごめんなさい。じーっと見られてたからつい。どうかしましたか？
Sorry, but you were just staring at me. Is everything okay?
いや別に…それっぽい雰囲気を出そうとしてただけだ。
Yeah, I'm just building atmosphere.
それより、頼んでた絵はできた？
Uh, anyway, you did the picture I asked for?
できました〜！
Yeah!
描きましたけど、それ誰なんですか？
Who's this a picture of anyway?
いま調べている事件の被害者だよ。
The victim from a case I'm working.
あっ、報酬はいつもの値段でいいよね？
Anyway, you're charging the standard fee, right?
悪いけど今回はツケにしといて。
Sorry, but can you put it on my tab?
でも前回もツケって言ってましたよね…。
But you put the last one on your tab too...
じゃあイナは特別に、１回だけタダで依頼を受けてあげるから。
Maybe we could do a trade then? I'll solve one case for you for free.
それよりも…歌がいいな〜。
Oooorr... I'll trade you for a song~
はい？
Huh?
だってアーニャさん最近ずっと怖い顔してますよ。
Come on! You've been so serious lately.
たまには息抜きしないと。
You gotta get loose sometimes.
私と１曲歌ってくれたら、絵は差し上げます。どうですか？
So one song with me, and you get to keep the picture. That's the deal~
そこまで言うなら…歌ってやるか！
If that's what you want, then alright!
大きな白いキャンバスに
I'm going to put a fiction collage...
虚構のコラージュを貼るよ
...up on a big white canvas.
どこからでも綺麗に映る
It looks beautiful from everywhere.
誇張された天使が居たよ
There was an exaggerated angel.
薔薇 人 歪んだ
Roses, people, distorted,
正しくなくても見えた
even though it didn't look right, it was visible.
生きるため立ち寄った美術館のセザンヌに
To live, I stopped by Cezanne at the art museum.
なんもわかんないな
I don't understand anything at all.
まだ知らずにいても描けた 赤
Even without knowing, I could draw it, red.
ずっと塗り込んだ
I kept on painting it over.
馬鹿 きっとそこだった
Fool, it must have been right there.
一筆書きの絵画だけどそこがいいな
A single-stroke painting, but I like it.
くだらない線だな
What a trivial line...
そのまま
Just like that.
きいて ほら かわ
Listen, see, side...
泣いて見えた朝
Morning that looked like it was crying.
ラララララララ
La la la la la la la
笑うより浮いた
Floated rather than smiled.
甘い殻の
From a sweet shell.
ギュッて咲いてから
Once it bloomed tight,
ギュッて泣いてから
Once it cried tight,
抱いてないてから
Once it cried in an embrace,
ラララララララ
La la la la la la la
嘆く壁に描いた
Painted on the wailing wall,
パブロ ピカソ
Pablo Picasso.
なぜか私のことだなって眺めちゃったよ
For some reason, I gazed at it, thinking it was about me.
これが欲しいなって感じたら
If I feel like I want this,
セザンヌの絵を希求
I long for Cezanne's paintings.
なんてね
Just kidding.
同人が囚われじっと見てたよ
The colleague was trapped, staring intently.
今 嘘を重ねられば
If I pile up lies now,
本物の意味あるのかな
will there be any meaning in what's real?
真実いだいたまま
Holding the truth within,
飾り落ちて床で死んでた
decorations fell and died on the floor.
じっと ずっと塗り込んだ
Steadfastly, I kept on painting over.
やっぱ ずっとよかった
After all, it was good all along.
いやらしい線だな
What an unpleasant line...
今もああ
Even now, ah...
きいて ほら かわ
Listen, see, side...
咲いて散った花
Flowers that bloomed and scattered.
ラララララララ
La la la la la la la
笑うように見えた
It looked like it was smiling.
受からぬ
Won't pass.
ギュッて抱いてから
Once it embraced tight,
ギュッて泣いてから
Once it cried tight,
抱いてないてから
Once it cried in an embrace,
ラララララララ
La la la la la la la
嘆く壁に描いた
Painted on the wailing wall,
パブロ ピカソ
Pablo Picasso.
私 嘘のピカソ
I am a false Picasso.
やっと来た。
Finally.
こんな不気味な場所で待たせないでほしいんだけど。
This is a creepy place to make someone wait.
現場を調べたらKFPの近くに寄るから、店の近くで待っててって言ったのに。
I told you I'd come to the nearby KFP after investigating the crime scene.
そんなの無理！
Not a chance!
アンタと話すだけでもイヤなのに、話してるところを人に見られたりしたらそれこそ最悪。
It's bad enough I have to talk to you. I don't want others to be around to see it.
そんなアンタが手を貸してくれるなんて意外だけどね。
I'm surprised you're willing to cooperate in the first place.
それは…例の殺人事件以降、いろいろ妙なことが起こってるの。
Yeah, well, ever since the murder, weird things have been happening.
アンタが解決してくれるんなら、こうやって会うのもやむなしよ。イヤだけど。
I figure if you can help solve it, then it's worth the trouble of meeting with you. Just barely.
妙なことが起こってる？
What weirdness?
「人の形をした黒い影が見えた」って報告が、うちの従業員からちょくちょく出てるの。
Some of my employees have been complaining about seeing a shadowy figure.
話によれば、最初は夢の中にそれが現れたんだけど、今は起きてる時も見え得るって――
They say it started with bad dreams, but now some are seeing it even when they're—
アーニャ！
Anya!
だ…大丈夫。それより…
I'm... fine. Don't worry about me.
これ見て。
Look at this.
まったくもう、アンタはいつも大げさすぎ…ん？
Hmph. 'Course. You're just always being overly dramatic... huh?
おかしいな。現場の証拠品は警察が全部回収したはずなのに。
Weird. I figured the cops would have already collected all the evidence.
この近くに住んでるKFPの従業員で、被害者のことを知ってる者は？
Did any of your employees who live nearby know the victim?
いない。
Nope.
分かった。新しい情報が入ったらまた教えて。
Alright. Let me know if you hear anything else.
ちょっと待った！
Wait!
それだけ？
That's it?
私の時間を奪っておいてタダで帰るつもり？
You're not even gonna compensate me for my time?
従業員のためかと思いきや、結局カネか。
I thought you were doing this to help your employees.
タダ働きはしない主義なの。
I'm still a businesswoman.
いま持ち合わせがないんだけど、代わりに歌で支払うっていうのはどう？
Well, I don't have any cash on me, but I can pay you in song.
ウソでしょ？
Seriously?
歌うの？
You think I'd want to sing?
アンタと？
With you?
イナは歌で喜んでくれたけどなー。
Ina accepted payment in song.
ただ、イナと歌うのは楽しいけど、
But then, singing with her is fun.
キアラと歌ってもなあ…。
With you...
それどういう意味？私の歌じゃダメってこと？
With me, what? You don't think I'm good enough for you?!
やってやろうじゃないの！ほら、きっちりと歌うよ！
Let's go, punk! You and me, right now!
全部 全部
It's all, it's all
アンタのせいだ
your fault again!
反吐が出るくらいにウザったいわ
You make me sick, I can't stand it anymore.
何かに縋って
I was a fool to rely on you,
諂って
to flatter you,
期待したアタシが馬鹿だった
And to expect greatness from you.
ご機嫌 お互いの
Greeting each other
八方美人
as two-faced people
連れように
out of sync
アンチな一生君
for an anti-life you
浅いキャパシティ
Shallow capacity
毎度おおきに
Thanks every time
詰まるところ人生ずっと地味
In short, life is always plain
憎たらしい！
I hate you!
痛々しい！
You're pathetic!
無視できないのがエゴ
I can't ignore my ego
腹立たしい
Infuriating
苛立たしい
Irritating
そろそろ飽きたしお互い様に
I'm tired of this, we're both to blame
ライクの反対は
The opposite of like is
無し
nothing
ニアイコール
near-equal
繋がれた証
proof of being connected
切り離せない関係
An inseparable relationship
反らしてしまいたいわ
I want to turn away from it
これはアイ・マイ・ユル
This is I, My, Yuru
ヘイトスピーチ
hate speech
匿名性の生命を
An anonymous life
生命に乗せてんだ
riding on a life
鳴り止まないサイレン
Unceasing sirens
近づく度に
every time I get closer
クラクションが
The horn is
ずっと邪魔ね
always in the way
だいたいアンタのことアタシ
Usually, for me, about you...
ダイダイダイダイダイキライ
I hate, hate, hate, hate, hate you!
オーマイガー
Oh my god,
情けない
how pathetic.
もはやバイバイバイバイバイしたい
I want to say bye, bye, bye, bye, bye!
脳内も
Inside my mind,
予測不能
unpredictable,
ゆえに
therefore...
カイ・カイ・カイ・カイ・カイは無い
there's no, no, no, no, no answer.
ウザい
Annoying,
アタシのことアンタ
you, to me...
ダイダイダイダイダイキライになった？
have you come to hate, hate, hate, hate, hate me?
全部 全部
It's all, it's all
アンタのせいだ
your fault again!
反吐が出るくらいにウザったいわ
You make me sick, I can't stand it anymore.
何かに縋って
I was a fool to rely on you,
諂って
to flatter you,
期待したアタシが馬鹿だった
And to expect greatness from you.
アイ・ミス・ユー
I miss you,
天地が
the world
ひっくり返っても
turned upside down,
ポイズン ポイズン
poison, poison,
サンキュー
thank you,
反面教師
bad example.
あと、アタシ一生消えてくんないわ
Also, I won't disappear forever.
よしよし いい子ね
There, there, good girl,
笑顔振りまきバラバラいい子ね
spreading smiles, a scattered good girl.
どけよ どけよ その本性は
Step aside, step aside, that true nature,
善悪の区別もつかないの？
can't you even tell good from evil?
検定方式で通ります
Passing by the test method,
感情に巻かれて
wrapped in emotions,
生涯 だいたい 報われないわって
life is mostly unrewarded,
当然の報いに食らっちゃった
hit by the natural consequence.
ヒトは
People are
鏡なんです
mirrors,
実のところ
to tell the truth,
依存は両便なんです
dependence is two-way.
シャットダウンしても付き纏う
Even if I shut down, it follows me,
己の弱さが不甲斐ない
my own weakness is so pathetic.
全部 全部
It's all, it's all
アンタのせいだ
your fault again!
反吐が出るくらいに止まんないわ
You make me sick, I can't stand it anymore.
いっそのこと切り離せた方が
It would be easier
楽なのに、な
if I could just cut it off.
だいたいアンタのことアタシ
Usually, for me, about you...
ダイダイダイダイダイキライ
I hate, hate, hate, hate, hate you!
オーマイガー
Oh my god,
情けない
how pathetic.
もはやバイバイバイバイバイしたい
I want to say bye, bye, bye, bye, bye!
脳内も
Inside my mind,
予測不能
unpredictable,
ゆえに
therefore...
カイ・カイ・カイ・カイ・カイは無い
there's no, no, no, no, no answer.
ウザい
Annoying,
アタシのことアンタ
you, to me...
ダイダイダイダイダイキライになった？
have you come to hate, hate, hate, hate, hate me?
全部 全部
It's all, it's all
アンタのせいだ
your fault again!
反吐が出るくらいにウザったいわ
You make me sick, I can't stand it anymore.
何かに縋って
I was a fool to rely on you,
諂って
to flatter you,
期待したアタシが馬鹿だった
And to expect greatness from you.
アイ・ミス・ユー
I miss you,
天地が
the world
ひっくり返っても
turned upside down,
ポイズン ポイズン
poison, poison,
サンキュー
thank you,
反面教師
bad example.
あと、アタシ一生消えてくんないわ
Also, I won't disappear forever.
はぁ、もう！誰なの？
Ugh, geez! Who is it?
はーい。
Come in.
アーニャ、ヤッホー。って、大丈夫そう？
Hey Anya. You okay?
なんか顔色悪いね。
You look kind of... pale.
大丈夫じゃないかもね。
Thanks... maybe not.
ちょっと横になったほうがいいんじゃない？
Maybe you should lie down for a bit?
周りをグルグル走ってあげるから、わための数を数えるといいよ。
I'll run circles around you so you can count the Watames.
心配かけてごめん。
Sorry for worrying you.
でも、今寝たらダメなんだ。
But I can't sleep now.
なぜなら、あと、もうちょっとでこの事件を解決できそうなんだから！
Because I'm so close to solving this case!
そう？
You sure?
そうかも、そうじゃないかも、わかんないけど、とりあえずヒントは揃ったんだ。
Maybe, maybe not, I don't know, but anyway, I have all the hints.
ほな難しいか。
Then it's difficult.
わため先輩、ほどほどにしておきましょう。
Watame-senpai, let's keep it moderate.
わためは悪くないよねぇ？
Watame did nothing wrong, right?
これが事件を解く鍵なんだ。探偵の直感がそう言ってる。
This is the key to solving the case. My detective's intuition says so.
でも、DNA鑑定では何もわからなかった。
But the DNA test didn't reveal anything.
じゃあ、これは何なんだ？
Then what is this?
これは何なんだ！
What is this?!
その布でそんなにお困りなら、あ、じゃあわためが食べてあげる。
If you're so troubled by that cloth, oh, then Watame will eat it for you.
ねえアーニャ、それちょっと見せてくれる？
Hey Anya, can you show me that for a second?
この布についてはわかったことはあるけど。うーん。
I've found out something about this cloth. Hmm.
それを教えたら、ちょっと休憩しない？
If I tell you, will you take a little break?
一旦仕事の手は止めて、私達と遊ぼうよ。
Stop working for a bit and play with us.
じゃあ、一緒に歌でも歌う？
Then, shall we sing a song together?
この街では、情報は歌で買うものみたいだし。
In this town, it seems information is bought with songs.
おお、楽しそう。
Oh, sounds like fun.
オーケー。その布には、魔力の痕跡を感じるんだ。
Okay. I feel a trace of magic on that cloth.
そんなバカな...
That can't be true...
忘れたの？アイリスはネフィリム。
Hey, I'm a nephilim, remember?
魔力を感じ取るなんてお手の物。
We get a bonus to detect magic!
あれ？アーニャもこの布が怪しいと思ってたんじゃないの？
You already had your suspicions about the cloth, didn't you?
そうだけどさ。
Yeaaaah...
でも、殺人事件と超常現象なんて混ぜたらダメなやつでしょ？
But supernatural stuff happening in a murder case? They're not supposed to mix.
そう？でもそういうアニメとかドラマも...
Really? But in some shows...
まあまあ、物騒な話はそのくらいにして、
Enough murder talk.
みんなで歌っちゃおう！
Let's sing~
ULTRA C
この路地を抜けろ awake now
Break through this alley, awake now
僕ら覚醒 アップデート hey
We're waking up, update, hey
ギラギラ光らせた
Sparkling, dazzling
いいな いいな そのカラット
I like, I like that carat
目立っちゃうな 自然に視線を独り占め
It stands out, naturally hogging all the attention
この手口は盗めない
You can't steal this method
答えなら「好きなだけ」が極まってく
If you want an answer, "as much as you like" is peaking
1秒前 完全アップデート ya ya
One second ago, a complete update, ya ya
不安グッバイ 自分以外は敵じゃない
Goodbye anxiety, nobody but myself is my enemy
折り句ご無用 指を立てろ
No need for acrostics, raise your finger
Ha~ 揺れろ運命
Ha~ shake, destiny
Ah~ あたらしいウルトラC
Ah~ a new Ultra C
その感情を燃料に
Using those emotions as fuel
勝ちの確信 駆け上がってく
Certainty of victory, climbing up
1秒前 完全アップデート ya ya
One second ago, a complete update, ya ya
この生き様で Make some noise
Make some noise with this way of life
見舞う We gotta 豪めく Go-Boy
Pay a visit, we gotta, brilliant Go-Boy
宿した熱狂は伝播する
The passion you've harbored will spread
幕開けは直後だ
The curtain rises right after
貰うは大喝采
We'll receive a huge round of applause
Ready? Get down!
覚醒 アップデート hey
Waking up, update, hey
独りきりじゃ just kidding
Being all alone? Just kidding
決めてたから dreaming
Because I had decided, dreaming
間違いだらけ勘違いもして
Full of mistakes and misunderstandings
ときめきをリテイク
Retaking the excitement
失っても continue
Even if I lose it, continue
支払った対価の自分あの日の
The me that paid the price that day
してないわけない後悔 胸に飾れ
Of course I have regrets, wear them on your chest
前向き直せ
Face forward again
捕らえて
Catch it
諦め悪いって
Saying you're a bad loser
信じてくれ
Believe me
青くもゆる僕は仄々
Burning blue, I am faintly glowing
時は経って 焦がれる心
Time passes, a yearning heart
誰だ誰だ 誰だ？ 誰だ？ 誰だ 出した？
Who is it, who? Who? Who? Who put it out?
出した？ お任せ
Put it out? Leave it to me
あたらしいイバラ Make some noise
New thorns, make some noise
有終の美より Heigh-Ho Let's Dance
Rather than a graceful end, Heigh-Ho let's dance
極した逆境に下剋上
Overthrowing from extreme adversity
轟く摩天楼
Roaring skyscrapers
上げるは大歓声
Raising a great cheer
Touch down!
燃やせ 革命 アップデート hey
Burn it, revolution, update, hey
Go round!
爆夜 革命 劇成 hey
Explosive night, revolution, dramatic creation, hey
以上がこちらで調べた情報です。
So that's everything I've got so far.
いかがですか？
What do you think?
ここは大空警察。
And so, here she visits the Oozora Police.
数々の難事件を解決してきた優秀な警察から、
With their stellar track record of solving mysterious cases like this one easily,
今回の事件に関するさらなる情報を得るべく、
she hopes that they can give her some leads.
探偵は警察署を訪れていた。
The detective was visiting the police station.
だから、事件の捜査は我々プロに任せておけばいいんだよ！
I think you should leave the investigating to the professionals.
何？被害者の服に魔力の痕跡があったって？
I mean, magical residue on the victim's clothing?
そうだ、そんなバカな話があるか！
Yes! That is very silly!
こいつ、次、自分自身が凶器かもしれないとか言い出すんじゃないですか、署長。
Next, she's going to tell me that SHE'S actually involved and might be the murder weapon.
それだ！
Wait, that's it!
はぁ？
Huh?
こいつ今、自分が凶器だって自白した？
Did she just confess to being the murder weapon?
よく分かんないっす。
I'm not really sure.
ボクが言ったのはただの冗談で...
I was just joking about that...
もしかしてボク、無意識のうちに真実をつかんでいたのか!?
Wait, did I subconsciously uncover the truth!?
お前天才か!?
Are you a genius!?
おや、これはいいよいよ事件解決...になってしまうのか?
Oh my, could this possibly mean the case is solved?
事件解決しちゃった!
I solved the case!
違う違う、私は凶器じゃないですよ。
No, no, I'm not the murder weapon.
異議あり! さっき自白しただろ!
OBJECTION! You already confessed!
私が言いたいのは、この事件にはまた別の古代兵器が関わっているかもしれないということ。
What I mean is, maybe there was another ancient weapon involved...
だから布に魔力が残っていたんだ。
That would explain the magical residue on the cloth.
なんだそういうことか...
I guess that makes sense.
僕が事件を解決できたと思ったのに...
But I wanted to be the one to solve the case...
まあ次がんばれよ。
Well, better luck next time.
でもなあ、現場の近くで変なものを見たっていう報告も届いてるんだ。
But we've also gotten reports of people seeing strange things near the scene.
その魔力の痕跡とやらが超常的な力によるものだっていうなら...
If the involvement of something supernatural explains the magical residue...
変な幻覚が見えた人がいるのもそいつの影響ってこと?
Does it also cover those weird visions people had?
それはまだ分かりませんが、謎は必ず解いてみせましょう。
I'm not sure yet, but I'm going to find out.
じゃあうちの捜査資料を持って行っていいよ。
Then we'll give you our case file to help out.
民間人にあげちゃダメっすよ!
You can't give that to a civilian!
でもこいつさ、なんか天才の匂いしね?
But she seems like a genius, don't you think?
さっきは僕のこと天才って言ったじゃないですかぁ...
But you just said that I was the genius...
どんな情報でも助かりますよ。
Any information you have would be useful.
ただし! 資料が欲しいなら...
Fine! But if you want our files...
タダというわけにはいかんな!
We need something in return!
これ、また歌う流れですか?
Could that thing be, perhaps, a song?
オレは 知らない
I don't know
何も 知らない
I don't know anything
何も 見てない
I haven't seen anything
誰も 見てない
I haven't seen anyone
空を 見ても 見えない夜の
Even if I look at the sky, on a night when I can't see
欠けた 月に うさぎ
The rabbit in the crescent moon
これは なんだ
What is this?
それが なにか
What is that?
ここが 魂
This is the soul
それで よろし
And that's just fine
走る 逃げる 逃がす 逸らす
Running, escaping, letting go, looking away
月の 欠けた 場所へ
To the place where the moon is missing
あらら あらら あらら あらら
Ara-ra, ara-ra, ara-ra, ara-ra
まあさ 責められなく
Well, without being blamed
さあさ 咎められなく
Now, without being rebuked
衝動 収まらず
Impulses not subsiding
なぜか なぜか 知らん
For some reason, I don't know why
最悪だ! ごちゃ泥足を踏んで脱いで踊れ
It's the worst! Stomp through the mud, strip and dance
最低か? なんでなんでっつってなんか何か高まって
Are you the worst? Asking why, why, feeling something rising
最悪だ! どうもこうも死ねよ勝手にしやがれ
It's the worst! Just die already, do as you please
最低か? やあもう本当最悪だだだだだだ
Are you the worst? Oh, it's really the worst-t-t-t-t-t
寝ても覚めても付きまとう
Haunting me awake or asleep
見える意識の裏側に
Behind the visible consciousness
大きく開いた黒い穴
A big open black hole
分かる 分かる 分かる
I understand, I understand, I understand
いいっす 許せん
It's okay, unforgivable
許す 許せん
Forgive, unforgivable
かわいい えへへ ふふん 怖い
Cute, ehehe, hmph, scary
リンゴ ゴリラ
Apple, gorilla
落語 ゴジラ
Rakugo, Godzilla
ラクダ ダボラ
Camel, dabola
ラマダ
Ramada
私たち 絶対に見てません
We definitely haven't seen anything
知ってません 聞いてません
Don't know, haven't heard
知ったこっちゃありません
It's none of our business
光をいっそ陰にひと突き
Might as well thrust the light into the shadows
許されざる思考を
Unforgivable thoughts
あてはまらない情
Emotions that don't fit
潜んで生きていこうじゃありませんか
Shall we live in hiding?
行動 名も持たず
Action, without even a name
狂騒 意味もなく
Uproar, without any meaning
永劫 自己満足
Eternal self-satisfaction
だから だから 知らん
So, so, I don't know
最高だ! 脳が硬化してんだぶっ壊して叫べ
It's the best! My brain is hardening, smash it and scream
最高か? なんでなんでっつってまごまごはねちゃって
Is it the best? Asking why, why, jumping around in confusion
最高だ! 好奇心で結構勝手に生きたれ
It's the best! Live as you please with your curiosity
最高か? やあもう本当最高だだだだだだ
Is it the best? Oh, it's really the best-t-t-t-t-t
昔々のお甘えつき
Once upon a time, a pampered child
前向き前向きのひとだかり
A forward-looking crowd
無邪気無敵の生まれつき
Innocent and invincible by birth
それが それが それが
That is, that is, that is
責任集合体
Responsibility Society
アンタもワタシも関係ない
It has nothing to do with you or me
責任集合体
Responsibility Society
楽しくやってりゃ無問題
If you enjoy it, there's no problem
勝手にやってりゃ問題ナシ
If you do it on your own, there's no problem
オレは 知らない
I don't know
何も 知らない
I don't know anything
何も 見てない
I haven't seen anything
何も...
Anything...
②責任集合体
② The Responsibility Collective
そういうことで、それじゃあ。
That's how it is. Well then.
超常的な力が殺人事件に関わっている？
A supernatural occurrence, happening in a murder case?
いやいやそんな、ねえ？
That's just unbelievable.
にわかには信じがたいが、今の手がかりから推理するとそういうことになる。
She had a hard time believing it, but all the hints said otherwise.
まだパズルのピースがピタリとはまらないこの不思議で奇妙な事件。
Still, there were pieces of this puzzle that refused to fit,
探偵は信頼できる情報源に頼ることにした。
so the detective turned to a reliable source for help.
あっ、来てくれたー
Hey, I'm glad—
……なんで君達まで？
—and why are you guys also here?
ゼータが来るって聞いたから、アーニャにちょっかいかけてやろうと思って！
We heard Zeta was coming over, and decided to bug ya!
はいはい。
Yes, yes. I see.
もー！つれないなぁ。
Aww, come on!
それはそうと……ゼータ、何か掴めた？
Anyway, Zeta, did you find anything?
もちろん！優秀なシークレットエージェントなので！
Of course! I'm not an elite secret agent for nothing.
イナの描いた似顔絵と大空警察の資料から、被害者の身元を特定できたよ。
Between the portrait from Ina and the files from the Oozora Police, I've been able to positively ID the murder victim.
でも、ちょっと変なんだよね。
But... what I found is weird.
変？
How so?
被害者の履歴を調べたところ、その人物は何百年も前の時代の人だったんだ。
Well, when I investigated their history, I found that they actually lived centuries ago.
でもその人物が、数日前に死体で発見された……話がつながらないよ。
So how they were also somehow murdered just days ago... it doesn't make any sense.
アーニャからもらった情報に間違いがあったとか？
Did you perhaps confuse your information? Or...
なるほど、やっとつながってきた。
Actually, things are finally starting to make sense.
えっ？
Oh?
一人の被害者が、過去と現在で二度死んだことになる。
A victim caught between two times.
誰かが時間と次元をねじ曲げて、そんな状況を作り出した。
One who died in two different ways.
なかなかできることじゃない……
Not many exist who can cause time and dimensions to warp in a way to make that possible...
でも君達なら可能でしょ。
...but you're one of them.
さすがは名探偵。
Well done, detective.
ちょっと時間がかかりすぎかな。
Took you long enough.
危うくネタばらしするとこだった。
I was this close to telling ya the whole thing.
レイネが書いてくれた、この匿名の手紙もいいヒントになったよ。
You helped enough with this "anonymous" letter about the murder.
えっ、バレてた？
O-oh, you figured out that was me?
書き方のクセで分かる。
I recognized your writing style.
待って、どういうこと？
W-wait, I don't get it.
ムーナと被害者にどんな関係があるの？
What does Moona have to do with the victim?
ムーナは、別の時空で殺された遺体を我々がいるこの時空へ移動させたんだ。
She took a murder victim from another space and time, and moved them into our dimension.
ゼータが特定した人物は、この世界線における同じ人物ってこと。
The one you IDed was this universe's version of the same person.
なるほど。でもどうしてそんなことを？
Uh... okay. But then why?
理由も気になるけど、それより確かめたいことがある。
That is an important question, but there's one I want answered even more.
ムーナが……私にあの夢を見せてたの？
Are you... responsible for my dreams?
それは違う。
No.
あなたがあの夢を見ていることを知って、私はあの夢が生まれる根源を調べてみた。
After I learned about your dreams, I used my powers to search for the source of them.
そして見つけたのが、次元の向こう側から声を届けようとする魂。
I found a spirit reaching out from time and dimensions.
私はその魂のために橋渡しを少ししてあげただけ……
All I've done is try to help them by making the bridge a little easier...
私も手伝ったよ！
With my help!
というか、私のアイディア。
I mean, it was my idea...
そう。
True.
ただやり方が悪かったのか、アーニャの見たいものが他の人にも見えちゃったみたい。
Though doing it this way has caused some of what you've been experiencing to leak to other people.
巻き込んだKFPの従業員には後でお詫びしなきゃ……
We're going to have to apologize to the KFP workers...
でもその魂が、どうして私に声を届けようとしてるの？
But why is the spirit reaching out to me of all people?
それは私に訊くことじゃないね。私が話すべきことじゃない。
It wouldn't be right for me to answer those questions. It's not my story to tell.
あの魂に心を開いてあげて。それだけでいい。
Open yourself up to the spirits, and they'll do the rest.
心をもっと開く方法なら知ってるよ！
I got a way to make yourself more open to spirits!
それって歌？
Is it through song?
え？なんで分かったの？
Huh? How'd you know?
まあ、勘かな。
Lucky guess...
想い返していた 思い出の中で泣いていた
I was looking back, crying inside my memories
不確かな夢と 孤独を抱えて笑ってた
With uncertain dreams and loneliness, I was laughing
この痛みも傷もいたいけな瞳も
This pain, these wounds, these innocent eyes too
無に帰してしまいそうな 僕らの日々を
Our days that seem like they'll return to nothingness
誰一人欠けることはない ちぐはぐな
No one is missing, in this mismatched
僕らの思いが 音になって繋ぐ
Our feelings turn into sound and connect us
こだまして
Echoing
忘れないよ 重なり合った日々を
I won't forget the overlapping days
あの日僕らは間違っていなかったんだと知る
Knowing that we weren't wrong that day
葬り去ってしまい込んだ 前線の光探して
Searching for the light on the front line that we buried away
君の声を聞かせて
Let me hear your voice
ここにいるって叫んでくれよ
Shout that you're here
その手を離さないで
Don't let go of that hand
世界に僕だけが取り残されてしまった
I was the only one left behind in the world
まただよな
It's happened again.
暗闇の中で立ち止まり
Stopping in the darkness,
手放してしまう
I end up letting go.
心が通じ合えない孤独感を
The sense of isolation from being unable to connect,
押し殺してしまうなら
if I'm to just suppress it,
一人でいたほうが楽に生きられたかな
maybe it would've been easier to just stay alone.
憧れ
Adoration,
理想に強く惹かれる
strongly attracted to my ideals,
感情が僕らを
these emotions of ours,
引き寄せてしまうのなら
if they are to draw us together,
応えて
then answer me!
凝らして 凝らして
Focus, focus...
まだ終わっちゃいないんだ
It's not over yet,
僕ら 延長戦なんだろう
we're in overtime, aren't we?
この音が途切れるまで
Until this sound fades away completely...
子どもの頃に描いたヒーロー
The hero I pictured as a child,
君の出番が待ってる
is waiting for your turn!
凝らして 忘れないよう
Focus, so I don't forget,
かき鳴らした日々を
the days I strummed away.
あの日 僕らは
On that day, we knew
間違っていなかったんだと知る
that we weren't wrong.
閉ざしてしまいこんだ一閃を
Searching for that flash of light
さがして
I'd locked away deep inside.
君の声を聞かせて
Let me hear your voice,
ここにいるって叫んでくれよ
shout out loud that you are right here!
その手を離さないで
And please, never let go of that hand.
魂に心を開け？
Opening up to the spirit?
簡単に言ってくれる。
That was a tall order.
探偵になる前の彼女の人生において、
In her life before being a detective,
他者に心を開くのは危険な行為だった。
opening up to someone was dangerous.
今でもその本能は変わらない。
That instinct still lingers.
結局何も進展はなかった。
This was getting her nowhere.
謎はまだ残っているが、
She still had questions she needed answered,
彼女はここのところ無理が続いていた。
but maybe she had wound herself up too much.
少し休まなければ。
She needed a break.
Hello everyone!
I'm Hatsune Miku, a virtual idol!
Well, that's what everyone seems to think,
but secretly I'm—
え？ミクちゃん？
Eh? Miku-chan?
アーニャちゃん！一緒に歌おう！
Anya-chan! Let's sing together!
I wake up to a call with my frilly outfit on now.
It's time I open up my eyes and start the day.
I hug the pillow now until happy feelings gone now.
I clumsy trip and now I fall into my bed!
With magical baton and a silver glitter ringtone,
I'll shout the magic words and set the world in place.
Whatever it may cost, there's no reason to stop,
for a world that I cherish and love!
Midst of light, we are here for the fight,
but until the sun sets over,
I can dry up your tears as I wipe them aside,
with a sparkle you'll ever find!
Give my M-A-G-I-C-A-L cure for piece of mind,
I'll always be honest being you every day.
So what if I fall and your tears get from blues,
so happy that I need to clean the cherry blossoms away!
Ha! Fighting through the night of having light the way,
could it all be so hard for me to find the way?
Just smile with enough to make my day,
so I send all the ray!
Catching all the brave and any pain take it all away,
turn up with love, fighting 'til the end!
And now, it's time for the moment you've been waiting for!
One, two, three, ready?
Miku Miku Beam!
On my own, without anyone to know,
how my job is not all rainbows,
but then I think about your smile!
Your words are so lovely!
I'm a magical bright intensely girl,
I will lead you to heal, go on and call my name!
When you find yourself going down a spiral,
I will blow it away, what was your done-of-a-thing-in-my-memory!
Yeah! Fighting through the night of having light the way,
could it all be so hard for me to find the way?
Just smile with enough to make my day,
so I send all the ray!
Catching all the brave and any pain take it all away,
turn up with love, fighting 'til the end!
Wait, so you're saying I've got to be brave?
As long as you can stay happy, I'm okay
I'm not gonna bend, ha!
I can be a cure for kissing your heart away
And I'll play and I'll sing you a whole new way
Your smile is enough to heal all my pain
So M-A-G-I-C-A-L Love Shot!
If you're feeling pain call my name I'll be by your side
Till I see your smile beam bright again
Urya oi! Urya oi!
1-2-3-4 Powerful Mikucchan!
Cyber Miku-miku go!
あー、眠いよ...
Ah, I'm sleepy...
夢... だった？
Was it... a dream?
知った、救いのない形だった
Understood, it was a form without salvation,
僕の聲は
my voice.
散った、狂いのない
Scattered, the unclouded
赤い血が流れているんだ
red blood is flowing.
ただただ襲い来る影ばかり満ちて
Only shadows are filling, coming to attack me.
抗う言葉も、立ち上がれない夜風
Facing words I can't resist, the wind that won't lift.
赤く光る場所へ、走り出したら
I left for a place that shines red,
ただ膝を抱えている君がいた
and there you were, just holding your knees.
だからENCOUNT、悲劇、決まった、天国へ
That's why an encounter, a tragedy, decided, to heaven.
不甲斐ない瞳きっとあの日、見つめた
Eyes that don't reflect, surely that day, I was staring at them.
君のせいは、早く、早く、早く、早く…
The days that followed, hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry...
身を揺らして
Shaking my body.
淡い、淡い、水面の向こうと
Faint, faint, beyond the water's surface...
知った、
Understood,
救いのない熱を持った僕の炎夏
my flaming summer that held a heat without salvation.
散った、
Scattered,
狂いのない貴方の瞳は醜かった
your unclouded eyes were hideous.
酷く、酷く、酷く...
Terribly, terribly, terribly...
ぼう線としてるその顔に
At that dazed face,
触れて
touching it,
見たかった
I wanted to see.
だからENCOUNT、悲劇、決まった、天国へ
That's why an encounter, a tragedy, decided, to heaven.
知った、救いのない形だった僕の聲は
I knew it, it was a hopeless shape, my voice...
奪い合う瞳きっとあの日の
The eyes fighting for one another, surely on that day
移ろった君のせいだ
it was because of you, who changed.
はやくはやくはやくはやくはやくはやくはやくね教えて
Hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry, tell me.
深い深い秘密の向こうへと
To the other side of deep, deep secrets.
奪い合う瞳きっとあの日の
The eyes fighting for one another, surely on that day
移ろった君のせいだ
it was because of you, who changed.
はやくはやくはやくはやくはやくはやくはやくね教えて
Hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry, tell me.
淡い淡い秘密の向こうへと
To the other side of faint, faint secrets.
白い光見つめていると
When I stare into the white light,
急な痛みに襲われる
I'm overcome by a sudden pain.
僕は私を保っていられなくなることなど
Things like me becoming unable to maintain my self,
それどこか私の身体が証明している
in fact, my very body is proving it.
初めに、安堵する君が見たい
First, I want to see you relieved.
次に、期待したい
Next, I want to have hope.
この場所で戦いなど起こっていない。
There was no major battle here.
少なくともこの世界線では…。
At least not in this timeline...
だが探偵には分かっていた。
But the detective knows...
彼女が見たものは決して夢ではないことを。
what she saw was no dream.
心の中にはまだ殺戮の匂いが漂っている。
The smell of the carnage still lingers in her mind.
かつての彼女にまとわりついていた。あの匂い。
It's a scent that was, at one time, so familiar to her.
探偵としての生活も今では順調だが、
That stench would still linger on her...
そうでなければあの匂いからは離れることができなかったでしょう。
if the detective's life didn't take a turn for the better.
今でも…あの頃の日々がリアルな夢のようにまとわりつく。
Even now... her days felt more like the real dream.
終わるべくして終わったおとぎ話。
A fairytale. Maybe one that deserved to end.
どこまで行っても彼女は、
Because, at the end of the day, she...
生まれ持った本質から逃れることはできない。
can never run away from her nature.
それでも今は違う。
But she's not just that anymore.
今の彼女には仲間がいる。
She has friends to thank for that.
それが、別の世界線の彼女とは違う点なのかもしれない。
Maybe that was what separated her from the other version.
もしかしたらあの子は、幸せに生きることのできた世界線があったのだろうかと、
And, maybe... that version of herself just wanted a ray of hope,
そんな一筋の希望を求めていたのだろうか。
to know that there was one timeline where things worked out.
そしてその幸せな世界線というのは、ここではないまた別の世界線のことかもしれない…
Or perhaps this was never about the detective...
考えが頭を巡るものの、答えが出ることはない。
so many thoughts run amok inside her head, but they're forever left unanswered.
何にせよ、探偵は自身の血塗られた過去を忘れることはないでしょう。
Whatever the case, the detective won't forget her bloody past,
しかしまた後戻りするつもりもない。
but she isn't going to revert to it either.
彼女はこれからも仲間とともに進む。
She will continue to move forward with her friends,
望んだ結末を迎えられなかった別の自分達のためにも。
and for all the variants who didn't get their desired ending.
探偵アーニャ・メルフィッサは、
The detective, Anya Melfissa,
明日に向かって生き続ける。
will keep on living for her own tomorrow.
Anya Melfissa Birthday Live 2026!
How did everyone like it? Oh my goodness.
やっと今年も参りました、アーニャの誕生日です！
It's finally here again this year, it's Anya's birthday!
いかがでしたでしょうか？
How was it?
This time, I tried to incorporate a little bit of story into my 3D birthday celebration.
And I think it turned out pretty nice, you know?
You get story part and also live part.
And I think it turned out pretty well, hmm?
And also, how was my new original song? Oh my goodness!
How was my new original song? It was good, wasn't it?
I hope you all liked it.
新曲もね、あの、歌わせていただきました。いかがでしたでしょうか？
I also got to perform my new song. How did you like it?
はぁ！
Haa!
Oh my god, I celebrated,
I celebrated my birthday with a lot of friends too this year.
Yeah, a lot of the girls came to celebrate my birthday...
...and also Detective Anya managed to solve that mission! Wow, she's got it!
Detective Anya, did you guys like Detective Anya as well?
Detective Anya was pretty cool but not as cool as me!
Oh my god and also, special guests! There were special guests!
Oh my god, I can't believe I got to sing with Hatsune Miku! Hatsune Miku-chan!
Oh my god she was really cute.
And also for the narration for my story part, Ueda Reina-san narrated.
Oh my god, Ueda Reina-san also...
ナレーションね、ストーリーパートのナレーションもね
As for the narration, the story part's narration as well,
上田麗奈さんが、えーやってくれました。ありがとうございます。
Ueda Reina-san, uh, did it for me. Thank you very much.
ミクちゃんとも歌ったし、いや盛りだくさんでしたね、今年。
I sang with Miku-chan too, it was really a lot this year.
Oh my god, lots of wild things happening on this year's birthday live. How did you guys like it?
How did you guys like it? Oh my gosh!
Yeah, I had a lot of fun!
But, I would like to make an announcement this year. It's the usual.
ここで告知があります。
I have an announcement to make here.
I have an announcement to make, let me make an announcement!
はい、こちら!
Yes, this one!
Oh my god, what is that? Who is that? Is that me? Yes, it is!
We're releasing some new merchandises too this year! What do we have?
Let's take a look at them shall we? そしてえっと、
Let's take a look at them shall we? And uh,
一つずつ見ていきましょう。まずは、こちらです！
let's look at them one by one. First is this!
Wow, it's a canvas art!
Study Time with Anya! The Canvas Art.
Oh my god, this illustration is so cute! It's illustrated by Lunar-sensei.
Lunar先生に、イラストを書いていただきました。かわいい！
Lunar-sensei illustrated this for me. Cute!
The theme is, you know, literary girl. Oh my god, so smart! So intelligent!
文学少女というテーマになっております。
It has a literary girl theme.
次は、こちら！Study Time with Anya! The Notebook.
Next is this! Study Time with Anya! The Notebook.
This is, I think this is my first notebook!
I've never had a notebook as a merchandise before! Oh my goodness!
Please use this lots for all your notes, for anything! いろいろメモしてね。
Please use this lots for all your notes, for anything! Take lots of notes.
オリジナルノートです。出ます！
It's an original notebook. It's coming out!
と、次は、こちら！It's a pen case! How cute is that?
And next is this! It's a pen case! How cute is that?
ペンポーチです！ペンポーチも初かな？
It's a pen pouch! Is the pen pouch a first too?
ノートも初だし、ペンポーチもなんと、えー初です！
The notebook is a first, and the pen pouch too, uh, is a first!
ぜひ一緒にね、あのノートと使ってください。
Please use it together with that notebook.
Use this along with the note, I think they would go really well together. Okay?
次は、こちら！今年もボイスが出ます！
Next is this! A voice pack is coming out this year too!
そして今年もえーアーニャが台本を書かせていただいております！
And this year too, uh, Anya wrote the script!
I wrote the script as usual, as usual for every year.
I wrote the script for this situational voice, so please get it! Please get it!
Oh yeah, the voice will be in Japanese but there will be scripts in Bahasa Indonesia, English and Japanese.
ちなみにボイス自体は日本語になりますけど、
By the way, the voice itself will be in Japanese, but
えーと台本もついてついてきます。インドネシア語と英語と日本語の台本があります。
uh, scripts are also included. There are scripts in Indonesian, English, and Japanese.
ぜひ聞いてください！
Please listen to it!
そしてフルセット購入特典はこちら！Oh my god, limited edition has...
And the set purchase bonus is here! Oh my god, limited edition has...
...what is that? A hand-signed autograph? Oh my god, it's the first for me!
Anya's first ever hand-signed autograph for limited edition! Please get them!
なんと今年はサイン入りです！今年はサイン入りです。
To my surprise, it's autographed this year! It's autographed this year.
なんと、なんと、なんと！初、初ですね、
Wow, wow, wow! It's a first, a first,
アーニャが自らサインをして。
Anya signing it herself.
初なのでぜひ皆さん、この機会で、ゲットしてください！
It's a first so everyone, please take this opportunity and get it!
Yeah, please get the limited edition! And for the standard edition...
...it includes a foil-stamped replica autograph, so don't worry if you miss out on the limited edition! Yeah!
と言うことで、グッズ紹介は以上です！
So, that's all for the merchandise introduction!
That's all for the merch!
Introduction!
And another announcement is that
my original song, the one that you guys heard,
um, it's called Enka or ENCOUNT by the way,
it will be releasing digitally!
It will be releasing digitally in like a few hours.
It will be releasing digitally at 12 AM your time zone
at 13th March.
Yay! Yippee! So in like, in like a few hours, yeah.
Yay! なんとね、デジタルリリース、
Yay! What's more, there's a digital release,
新曲のデジタルリリースもあります。
there's also a digital release for my new song.
13日の0時です。
It's at midnight on the 13th.
よろしくお願いします。
Please look forward to it.
そしてこの後、メンバーシップで配信もするのでぜひ見てください。
And after this, I'll be streaming for members, so please watch.
There will be a special encore for members only after this!
So members, Melhomies, let's go! There will be a membership-only stream after this!
So please come and watch, it'll be in 3D by the way.
So you guys might want to check it out.
Yippee!
Okay, are you guys ready? Are you guys ready?
Well, this live is ending, but we still have membership after this.
So I will see you guys there.
For members, I will see you guys there.
And for non-members, thank you so much for coming and for watching my 3D birthday live!
I hope you guys enjoyed it!
Thank you! Thank you!
And I wonder if you guys also posted a lot using the hashtag. I sure hope you guys did.
Yay! Thank you so much!
And... おつくリス！ Bye bye!
And... Otsu-kris! Bye bye!
おつくリス everyone!
Otsu-kris everyone!